Jennifer Mendez

Bayonne, New Jersey, United States



jenniferjael@hotmail.com



2012087981



linkedin.com/in/jennifer-mendez-52340498

Summary

Eight years of professional experience that includes, telemetry interpretation, maintaining compliance with required documentation, and appropriate communication with patients and physicians.

Seven years of professional experience as secretary. Responsibilities include accounts payables, data entry, and payroll preparation. Also, the ability to play multiple roles with broad range of analytical and creative skills.

Experience

Electrocardiography tech

Jersey City Medical Center - Barnabas Health

Hotel Specialist

Bardy Diagnostics, Inc. Sep 2020 - Present (6 months +)

Holter analyst

Select Medical Sep 2015 - Mar 2020 (4 years 7 months)

Holter analyst

Select Medical Sep 2015 - Mar 2020 (4 years 7 months)

Holter Analyst

Select Medical Sep 2015 - Mar 2020 (4 years 7 months)

Administrative Secretary

Roberts Variety Inc Aug 2006 - May 2013 (6 years 10 months) Invoices and bill of ladings Payroll preparation Accounts payables Deposits slip preparation

Education

University of Phoenix

Accounting, Accounting and Finance 2012 - 2015

Skills

Healthcare • Hospitals • Customer Service • Strategic Planning • Healthcare Management